

# Rodrigo

Developer



14 July 1983



Londrina - PR, Brazil



+55 43 999-108-629



http://goo.gl/F2v0o5



rodfersou@gmail.com

## About me -

I am passionate about the art of creating computer programs.

As you can see by looking at my experience, I worry much more about building a solid foundation of knowledge than work just with a particular language. I consider myself able to accept the challenge of working in any environment, language, database or platform.

**Design Patterns** 

Javascript

Python

**CSharp** 

Delphi

Java

**CSS** 

SOL

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

### **interests**

Good challenges, which demand concentration and focus on quality deliveries.

### education

2011-2012 Web Development Specialization course. **UTFPR** Use of offline web pages in the inventory of assets process. 2008-2009 Software Engineering and Database Specialization course. UEL Generating code from a class diagram to an object-relational mapper. 2002-2006 Computer Engineering Graduation. UNOPAR Adaptive assistant to access classroom tools. 2000-2001 Data Processing Technical course. **CEETEPS** Development of a library management system.

experience	
2015-Atual	Team leader Simples Consultoria Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2014-2015	Software architect  Anicet Corporação Analysis and development of big data systems and generation of market- ing information for e-commerce. (Python / MongoDB)
2012-2014	Developer AVADORA digital Analysis and development of web portals. (Python / Zope / Plone)
2013-2014	Systems Analyst AGILI Softwares para Área Pública Analysis and development of systems and web portals. (CSharp / Oracle)
2011-2012	Senior Systems Analyst MÓDULOS RECAP SOFTWARE LTDA Development and maintenance of ERP for tire retreaders. (Delphi / Firebird)
2011-2011	ABAP Developer PADO SA INDUST. COMERCIAL E IMPORTADORA Customization of SAP ERP screens and reports. (ABAP)
2009-2011	Systems Analyst Maxwell Bohr Instrumentação Eletrônica Development of applications for automation devices. (Python / C / C $++$ )
2009-2009	Systems Analyst ADVISE DO BRASIL Development and maintenance of application for automated processing of electronic texts. (Delphi / SQL Server)
2008-2009	Systems Analyst  Development and maintenance of GPRS and Satellite messaging server.  (CSharp / SQL Server)
2006-2008	Developer Amcor Flexibles Brasil LTDA  Development and maintenance of ERP for flexibles industry.  (Progress 4GL)
2003-2006	Senior Systems Analyst  Development and maintenance of ERP for vehicle dealers.  (Progress 4GL)

#### languages

English Understand Well, Speak Well, Read Well, Write Well. Spanish Understand Well, Speak Reasonably, Read Reasonably, Write Little. Understand Reasonably, Speak Little, Read Little, Write Little. Japanese